He said that there was a witness that waited. Yeah, she ran the red light. Yeah, I spoke with an insurance yesterday
and I'm not on my dad's insurance. Okay, so I'm not sure I'm waiting on a call.
What did your dad talk to already? They're gonna tell me who covered you. Did you talk to him already?
Yeah, okay. Did you explain to him why you were driving? Yeah. What was your version that you gave him?
Like, what did you tell him about that? Well, they didn't exactly tell me. I didn't ask you. No, I just told him that I used to work.
Okay, because if you were to send like, oh, it was just a one-time thing that borrowed the car. Okay, then that would've been a little bit better.
I mean, we're basically gonna go off of our state fund. Yeah, we're basically gonna go after his insurance company.
You know, we're gonna make them liable for everything. So that way, you know, all state plays a small role in this.
That way you don't want to be affected with insurance. Okay, so basically, so if he's in English, so basically what I tell him is that we're gonna go against the state fund.
This is the only thing that, the only thing that, the people in the state don't want to get a big part in this.
Okay.
Now, the only thing that we're gonna have to clean up a little bit is that with Luis, I said that he used the car to work.
Oh, look, what is this? They did a recorded statement, right?
Yeah, but I'm not sure at all.
Because what I would like for you dad to kind of see if he could do and maybe clean it up.
And then you, and then he clarify, then hopefully you didn't, you know,
so that they don't have a problem.
No, no, no, no, yes, but then Austin will think that they include him to the police and he's gonna go up more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But if you don't, it's not marvellous.
No, it's not.
No, he was driving his dad's van.
And he has all state and I was asking him what he had said to all state
Because if there's additional coverage or something that way all state might want to help out
So his dad has different shirts. This dad has all state
And but he has all state as well. No, he doesn't have additional coverage, right?
You don't have your other policy more, right?
One other with a vehicle? No, no, no, he just has all state
He's on the all state policy. No, he's not
Do you have other insurance? So let's say I borrowed your car. I have liberty, neutral
But maybe your car has all state. So I've liberty mutual but your car is all state. So do you have any other coverage?
for yourself? No, I
Had just can't really like
Month ago, I still have like the renters, but I don't have a lot of automobile number
I see so he never he has
So there is only one coverage all state there isn't anything on there that
Excludes you from driving right?
Okay, that's good
I guess Ken is Nelson's the adjuster
The adjuster
Don't talk to stay calm
No, I mentioned they wanted me to talk to him like they wanted me to call the insurance, but I guess it was too early
Yeah, though because they're gonna do a recorder stable now
Okay
Which is never in your best interest and since that guy was trying to say that you ran the red light or something
Yeah, yeah, that was very long
So you want to wait until we get the
Good things I had a statement
Was it sliding everything? Do you have the contact information with that witness? Yeah, I have to have your information
I don't have a copy of that statement
But she stayed to the coast she stayed until the cops showed up. Yeah, good
She's actually an insurance agent
Yeah
Well
Yeah, they're like the lady
But how many people were in the other car?
Let's see
Okay
Sounds good. Let's see
There's four people in the other vehicle. Yeah, there's two adults in two menus or
You
I'm sorry, what six and ten you said yeah between six and five two adults two adults
How many people in your car?
Okay
The car's not drivable
You're just like it's just max
I'm not even aware of the door
You're not
Oh
No, okay now how would you get to the hospital? Were you transported or you drive yourself for that?
Which hospital
You
You've actually taken there or something
Okay
Okay, um, did you treat anywhere else or just the hospital? What's it?
Okay, I do want to go like I'll go back
You get like
Nine zero three two way where is that that's normal
Okay
Right there
Over there. Yeah, right there where your fingers
We
Daniel Jan
eight nine zero three two four five two eight
Okay, got it
Oh, get them on us. I work at a UPS and Jimmy John. Oh, that's right. We have two jobs
Okay, it's got the UPS season
It's almost ending
Jimmy John those are working out something
Jimmy John's no, it's firehouse soaps that I love
Yeah, I really could try this it
There's no more I don't guarantee there's no one out there. I can make sounds in the front of them
under a mini
Okay
What are your current injuries
Um, just like a back it's a back strain like all of it just feels um
Okay, so you have to be very specific and you go see the doctor
Because they actually count each section of your back
You know what I mean? So when you when they're deciding on a settlement offer
They actually look at the codes for each thing. So upper back maybe code number one two three four
Lower back maybe seven seven seven seven seven little back maybe code number six six six six
Okay, so lower back lower back. Okay
And where just like lower back
Maybe lower mid mid back. Okay, so make sure you tell them lower and mid back
Anything with your neck or no, not yet. Okay, or if it does come any headaches or anything. No, okay
Have you ever had any prior injuries?
Um, I was going to the doctor because I had a back pain. I still had back pain
Okay, did they ever have an MRI? They had a
I have x-rays, but I don't know my results
And do you know why you're having this back pain? Do you just sleep funny or something?
No, I've been having it for for years like it's just
Like it's always like something that goes up to physical doubt
You see a like I'm comforted. Um, do you see a
Family doctor or yes, it was a family thought you'd buy my house. I'm still waiting on my results
Okay
And what were you driving? It was a
Nissan Quest ban in 2006 and they're sending you the info
Yeah, you can't log in and get it though
To to all state yeah
Um, I don't know my dad
Okay, of course
And what kind of car hit you? It was
2000 red Honda Civic
Got it. Okay
Okay
I
Know you have the two jobs, but it's just very important that you treat
Because that's just determinant of your settlement
Okay, so
If you go one time to the doctor then they'll give you a very low settlement
You know what I mean if you go multiple times then they give you a higher settlement
But if you miss appointments because I know you have two jobs and everything
Then they're not going to give you very much of a settlement at all
Right as long as I mean as long as it's before 12
Okay, good. Okay, I still feel like
Come back needs, you know, it's good
Okay
No
So traveling on Bonneville crossing Las Vegas Boulevard so
Bonneville going east or west
Um, where are you coming towards?
It's East
So this is uh, this is Bonneville, Las Vegas Boulevard is going this way
So you're going towards like sunrise matter
I was going towards like um
Oh the east canary going towards like that direction
Yeah, okay
First of all, yeah, we're the sun, so we're the sun, right?
Yeah
So you spun?
Yes, but I don't know if I spun out once
like or just
Like this
Here I just spun out like this
Okay, hold on
You're the green car
So you stayed still on Bonneville?
Yeah, I just don't know the car and nobody was
I got out of the car, but once they started yelling at me, I just like I just had to back through my car
I was very uncomfortable
Okay
So uh, first of all
Let's see
How can I read this? What is it? BMX Lewis?
Yeah, BMX Lewis, that Nieto, Agino, Dotho
You
You ever have any other prior accidents?
No
Never ever
I
I was a passenger, but like not me driving or anything like that
Oh, what was that happen?
That counts too
I think you was like 2014
I was with my girlfriend's dad
We're on the freeway and he didn't pay attention and he hit a car
This old front end was just mashed in
Oh, that's it
Okay
That's like the only accident in the middle of the car
Got it
I see
Any car criminal history
I see that
Where's the car now?
All right, I have it parked on my girlfriend's house
Okay
Do you know that?
It's uh, 2021, 14, Berkeley, Abbey
So 2114? Yeah
I
Come on in
Okay, but you can still put in a text line, right or no
Yeah, is it the so-and-so killer mark?
Yeah
Okay, thank you
Yeah, you guys can always turn it on
I
Don't
You're going to stand by.
I would from one side,
It's going to be like this,
there
for
that you're going to see more in this video, right?
Because in this video, you're going to see how it works.
Now, I don't think that if we're going to start something,
I don't know if it's a pain,
if you're going to be a doctor,
and you're doing it now,
I have a 7, a 1, 8, a 1,
and you're doing it again in 2, 3, 10,
and you're just going to have a pain,
you just have to carry them down a little.
Because the Walk hurts too much,
especially if you're going to be in sleep,
andWORK your breath,
you have to grab the hangover for them to get tight.
As far as time goes,
you're going to lose your mind but we're not.
It's going to dope the EM Ride away.
You realize you're going to have to love this breathing.
Because if you're doing this,
So it's better now when you try to do this, and that you're on the line right, and you see exactly what you're doing,
but what you have to do so that you don't get used to it.
Because the sections are a bit...
...they won't learn anything, they ain't no scribes or anything, they don't get used to it anymore except to hold or grab the wood tight.
It's all wider.
Maybe he created...
Maybe taught you how to live with people in the past.
Yes, just given that theory.
Because we're trying to add up the modules that are working,
They will help us by much use of our windows.
This one because now we already wanted to move.
Your house is expensive, because when you rent it, you get bit by bit.
What income?
you
enough
no
you
So you realize that what I do, I take care of them is that they are going to therapy to start this week
and the doctor, so that everything is discussed.
I will talk about that week, and what is going to happen again, one, two, two,
go on your journey and go back to San Luis, we have the right hand with the whole body.
Yes, we are going to give it to you, we are going to give it to you.
Okay.
Okay, let's see.
Do you want to treat near your house or near...
I'm going to go like near your house then.
Yeah, I can go.
Okay.
That's good.
And I'm going to take it.
Yeah.
So you're not going to give it to person, so that's what I'm going to do.
Okay.
No, I can't believe it.
I realize that there is no way for the services to be recovered.
That's the way I do it.
The way I do it is that if you don't recover anything from the safety of this type of person,
there is no way for the services to be recovered.
Neither the doctor nor the doctor.
That's the way I do it.
Are you off today or are you working?
Yeah, I'm working today.
Okay.
About 12.
12?
Okay.
We could give him an appointment set up for tomorrow, I guess.
Say tomorrow.
Yeah, tomorrow.
There is going to be like one doctor that you need to go see, but you only need to see him once a month.
Yeah, I told him.
Okay.
Yeah.
He has a family trip on Kondras, the night to the 15th, so I was trying to see if we could get him in before that.
So the car effect will be like 10 times a month, right?
I'd say it's normally three times a month a week and then it goes down to two times and then one time.
Okay.
Do you think we have the case or the case?
It all depends.
So let me give you one second, I'm trying to make your appointments.
Okay.
So first of all, I wanted to make sure that you get us a vehicle estimate because we want the estimate to be as high as possible.
That shouldn't have an issue, right?
As high as possible.
But I don't think the first time.
Okay.
Cool.
No worries in.
But if you do get an estimate from all state or anywhere, just give us a copy of it.
Okay.
You're going to get it on here, so don't worry about it.
You'll get this.
So let's see.
Vehicle.
Any medical bills.
Accident.
Vehicle estimate.
Okay.
We got all of this is your homework right here.
You're going to get a copy of it.
Yep.
Okay.
Can you text messages of the pictures?
Two pictures?
Yeah.
522.
This is going to give you a number.
702.
522.
05.
That's 7.
522.
05.
7.
4.
So.
Okay.
No.
She's actually are sent the version of what happened.
Or that's the thing that the person was working on the phone...
that was a claims of emergency.
You can see.
Best interview.
So
Yep, we're texting you.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, can we put it on our file?
Okay.
You can save that text line as our phone number like attorney or whatever law firm so that you can contact us.
So it's a text line only if you call nobody will pick up.
Okay, because people were like, I keep calling and I'm like, what number did you call?
Right.
So you can call the main line when you need to call us.
I'll just take a business card.
Okay.
I'll call a door.
You can speak to the gesture about the property damage.
Just don't talk to them about the accident or your injuries.
So if they say, hey, we want to come out and inspect your vehicle or we want to go and give you money for the vehicle or give your rental.
That's totally fine.
Yes, the car.
If they ask you about injuries or how the accident occurred, here's my attorney's number.
Okay.
So we're just about the injuries and are they asking about what else?
Like just the injury, right?
Yeah.
Just don't, nothing about the injuries.
Only about your car.
Not even about the accident.
If they say, hey, we're going left or right.
Well, don't even talk to them about the accident.
Okay.
So with the vehicle, yes.
Yes.
In the morning before 11 as he works.
Perfect.
Can you go in tomorrow at 10.30 to the doctor?
As long as I'm not before 12.
You need to, like, 11.30, 11.30?
Yeah, my 11.30.
Oh, yeah.
What time do you start work?
I start at 12.
Yeah.
Okay.
So you might want to get dressed up for work, then.
Yeah.
Okay.
I just have to wear a vest.
So people seem to think that, hey, someone hit my car.
They should get my car fixed.
It doesn't always happen that way.
So they're not going to go fixing your car.
They're not going to pay for your car if they don't know that they did it.
And who knows what happened on the police report.
And they still may not sometimes.
I have one client.
They were fighting until the end.
Five months to get their car fixed.
So we can always open a claim under your dad's insurance trying to get the car fixed as well.
That might be faster, but you had to pay the deductible.
And then they have to fight to get your deductible back.
Okay.
So do you want us to do that, then?
To open a claim under your dad's insurance so that you can get your car fixed faster?
Um.
So basically, they own the vehicles of all state steps and they would just take off the 500 and pay them the remaining dollars, right?
If it's total, they would look at the blue book value and then pay them the blue book value of the car,
unless there's some kind of upgrade.
Like, I just fixed the transmission.
I put $2,000 and there's a receipt for it.
Or I upgraded the subwoofer and here's a receipt for the subwoofer or whatever.
Okay.
So then they'd look at the blue book value and they just give you the blue book value of the car.
So basically, it says that if you want to wait, you can wait.
But if you want to buy another vehicle or something, you can return it to the car.
Like if I gave you a car.
Do you have full coverage for the car?
No, no.
No, nothing.
Okay.
This is like a building on that vehicle.
So there's no way to get the car to go.
So the other vehicle has a corn vehicle, so there are other vehicles.
So the other vehicles on that has full coverage.
So that car is basically just a vehicle.
Yeah, you had to wait for State Farm.
Yeah, no car until State Farm says, yeah, we did it and it could be months.
That's why you get that coverage.
You know what I mean?
Otherwise, because some people don't, because like my mom's car is like 2 grand.
Go ahead and crash and do it.
I'll buy a new car.
You know what I mean?
I'm not going to go pay extra amount of money to go and show a crappy car.
So that's why people put the liability on there, but then they had to go buy their own car after a while.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's only good if it's a nicer car.
You know what I mean?
If it's like a cheap dumpers that you're like, I just drive around just to put it around the neck.
I believe it's fine.
But we still need to see your declaration page.
Your insurance declaration page.
So when you get it from your dad, it's on here too.
Okay.
So yeah, you're not going to get a rental or anything until all State decides on it.
It could be months.
Don't file bankruptcy.
It's not a good idea.
You're going to take your money.
You're going to file bankruptcy until you get your money, spend it, and then file.
Okay.
So we talked about this briefly earlier, but I need you to go to the...
When you go to the doctor, you're going to go to two different doctors, a chiropractor, and a regular doctor.
They're different doctors.
Kind of like if you're going for eye doctor or your foot doctor, they're not the same kind of doctors.
The one that's the most important is the one that you're going to tomorrow.
It's okay.
The medical doctor.
Yes.
One second.